Welcome to the section JPA with hibernate in debt this is the main section of this course.
All the sections and dealing of our setting you up to be able to make the best use of this section in
the section you'd learn the basics of entities and the different annotations.
You learn how to create relationships between entities and also how to define inheritance hide read
keys people learn management and persistence context in that we will also discuss about the various
ways of creating data from the database using J.P. J.P. Cuil they do queries and criteria API.
We will understand transaction management and also how to do performance tuning for you AJP application.
We will also discuss how we implement caching with Fossilman.
And the second Lebel caches the home folder for this specific section is 0 2.
JP It wants it once you get into this section you'd see the details of all the eighty five steps and
the complete code example at the end of the section.
Also present we did backups at different stages of this specific section.
I welcome you to the most important section on this cause and I will see you in the full step.