Let's create a project which would serve as the starting point for all at once stupid stuff we would
want to create a main project with our I'm using sping good to go door to door and.
It's fine to use any question which is about that group ID and crookedest coming 28 minutes to be hyper
knit and the artifact name.
I'm just giving it us all.
So it's Group ID coming.
When did I hibernate the artifact name.
I'm giving it us more.
That's basically the name of the application that we're creating.
What I've already done is I've chosen in three dependencies who rob JP hitched to.
So these are the three dependences that you would need once you choose this dependencies.
We are all set to get rocking and rolling and click and it will download a zip code.
We have done this multiple times earlier so it should be ready for you.
You can import this into your eclipse.
How do you do that.
I have extracted the zip and placed it on some folder on my hard disk.
What I need to do is do a file import existing Maimon projects choose the next and choose the directory
where you expect that this file to have extracted it in 20 minutes get and hibernate with spring boot
0 2 GPA it grants that to follow where extracted the it do.
And I am importing it right now.
I'm clicking the finish.
This would import the project so it could bring Mavin into picture and make an orderly departure that
example and it would import everything that is needed to execute this project.
If this is the first time you are using that to pursue question of spring boot this might really take
a little while because this would download all the dependencies onto your local mayor with repository
and use them to create your project once the project is created.
It would look something like this you have two main Jowa.
This is where we would put all call in all up production code so spend resources this way we would put
all the configuration.
The application properties which is already present in there.
If let's say I would want to quote something about spring I would want to go to the something about
hibernate or that compilation can be done in application to properties.
We also have source Jowers as Java is the place where all this code would go.
We would write a lot of uniters during this code and all the tests that we would be writing would be
present in all this.
Show all the test code that we would write over here will not be really part of the deployable.
What do you mean by deployable.
When our code goes to production we would create a job or over all that this code will not be part of
that job.
Our work dress code is to ensure that all the code is working fine.
It does not really need it to run your application in production.
Other than that you would see maybe in dependencies which are present in here.
You have a wide variety of Mavin dependencies which are coming in because we chose three dependencies
in here.
Right rituals G-B G.P.A. do and Rabbe.
So if I open a pondered XML you'd see that there are those dependencies to be started in AJP.
So I wrote web and teched these had three things we treat you with.
And these are the three things which are present in here.
In addition always spring would add in a test dependency.
So the spring initialiser by default.
Add to that dependency on the standard test.
This is the one which we'll be using to write are you need yes to make sure that you have your application
running what you can do.
They might piggishness do it right click on it and see it run s g on it.
Just so this would launch up a test.
This test would launch up something called Spring boot context and this would check whether everything
is just fine or not.
If the first time you're locking it up it will take a little while.
So let's be a little patient with it and or some time you'd see that the application will launch.
And if I want to see the control look into windows show view and I can bring up the control.
You can see the console in here.
With all the load that is being printed there is a lot of log which is coming in here.
The generated bad shows are green but the shows J and it has succeeded.
The other thing you can also do is to add more piggish and rightly Granice job application and see that
you would be able to ram that Texas film.
What I recommend you to do is play around so try and see what's in here try and spend some time looking
at the folder structure and see what is in the palm read SML and other things like that and I will see
you in the next step.