Come back in this step let's create a simple entity for something called of course during the next steps
we would be playing around with these concepts called coursers students reviews and things like that.
These are very simple things to understand right.
Instructors create courses students do the quarters and leave reviews.
That's basically the concept.
And let's start with creating an entity for a cause.
So I'd start with creating a new class so let's create a new class and I would want to call this code
and all the entities because we'll be an entity entities like bean plus plus a typical java bean can
be used for any purpose right.
I can use it to store data to the database or I can take the data from the database put it in it and
use it to transfer the data to other leaders and lot of other things entities the specialization of
the bean.
We use an annotation at entity to define that us being is an entity so this is the entity in addition
this is like any other our being.
But we use an entity in addition to make this an entity import entity.
Jack's persistence and inside the code all the different fields that I would want.
Let's start with the ID field in relational design.
All table should have primary key primary key basically is something which is used to uniquely identify
a row in that table.
And the way we define primary keys is by using an ad to indicate that this is an ID field this is the
primary key.
The other thing I would want to make sure is I would want to shape the agenda this for us so I'll say
it generated value.
I would not want to assign an ID field.
I would want to generate that for me so I'll say a generated value.
The other field I would want to start off with is name a private string name.
We basically have a course with a long ID and a private string.
And those are the two fields that we would want to use.
Now create a simple constructor public course.
I don't want others to provide the ID.
I only want them to provide the string.
That's a constructor I would want to define what is using the courts class will provide a name and hibernate
would provide them.
So this dot name could do it for this being alone.
We would do this manually.
Let's have a translator for the name created for the name.
Let's have a good answer to that as well.
So General getters and setters for name.
So now we have to get a sense it does for the name.
All chief does generate all chiefdoms are rightly thought to generate and I would want to now generate
a get and settle for ID for ID.
I only want to generate get that because I don't want others to say that.
So I'll choose only to get to that.
We have getters and setters for any gaitered for ID.
We have a contractor one of the things DP mandate is a default constructor what would happen is when
I provide a constructor the default argument constructor that jowled typically provides will no longer
be available.
To counter that I would need to provide a default no argument constructor.
This construct will be used by G.P.A. to create this.
This is one of the things which is mandated by JP.
You need to have no argument constructor protected will ensure that other classes which dont pinheaded
from court will not be able to use de-construct be defined because the entity in the next step will
create a repository so that we can access the data from the court.
We can create courses delete courses and things like that to you in the next step.