Welcome back to the previous step redefined a course entity in this step.
What we do is we create a repository so that I can manage the courses I can create courses delete causes
and things like that.
Let's quickly do that.
So I want to create a new Jawa class I'd want to call this code repository but this would be managing
the code.
And today I would call it code repository and I would want to put it in a package or be more repository
to all the repositories that would be creating you'll be creating it in the package repository.
So let's go it.
Finish this in any repository class what we would want to be able to do is to talk to the entity manager.
So we would need to first have the entity manager auto add in.
How do I do that.
I a wide entity manager.
And I just called this manager or you can just call him.
So this is kind of the convention which we use you can either call it entity manager or just him.
If you look at all the examples traditionally they would be using it.
So let let's use that as well in this code.
So now I've done a complete shift or organized import and you see that the manager is imported in and
or the site is also in.
That's good.
So we now have the entity manager.
There are three methods that we would want to create in the course deposit.
One is find by ID we want to pass in an ID and get the course for that specific ID.
So I would want be able to pass in an ID one and get the call saying J.P. 806 I would want to be able
to save accounts.
So this statement that I would want to be able to use to insert the codes as well as I would want to
be able to abate of course.
So whether I would want to insert a new code or I would want to update an existing code.
I would want to use the same method delete by id method I would want to be able to pass in an ID and
delete it.
So these are the three methods that we would want to create in the next few steps for no what I would
want to focus on is defined by it.
So let's create this public court find by ID.
I would want to return the because for that specific.
What is the method in and the manager can make use of the manager that if you look at the entity manager
there is a fine demand code.
We will look at all the other method to chaplets and in the entity manager a little later in a basic
discussion on into the manager.
For now lets use the find method which is present in the entity manager.
I would say into the manager that fine what is the class of the end of the its course not as I would
want to find a course whose primary key is this.
And I would want to return that back.
What we are doing is defining a simple Find method.
We have done this earlier as well when we were taking the intellection BJP.
Now what we'll do is we'll try and use discours repository when we launch the application.
So we have defined method defined.
Now I would want to use this find by ID to get a detail of a code how do I do that.
I can go to the day of my application and the application what I'll do is make it implement something
called a command line run.
So I put the command line in and I would need to implement a couple of methods of control one or common
one and add and implement it and a third or what.
Here I would want to make use of the cost repository using spring right the way we would do that in
spring is we would auto wire it in.
So in my application or I will do is at Wired or most important that everything is ultimately Polder.
And now I can make use that the repository Dorte find by ID can I find by the way how many did I find
right now.
No we don't really have any data defined right now.
So what I'll do is I'll create a course within the depth of them and do remember how we created the
data.
The initial steps of the JP stuff what we need to do is we need to create a new file.
So what I'll do is I'll create a new file called Data Rescue.
It is in us kill file.
I'll call this date or not.
See we'll finish and all here I'll say insert into course for now there's only two fields ID.
Come on name and I would say use ten thousand one comma it's say JP in fifty's bartending.
Use a single code not double code.
So this should be a single code.
The other one is that you should end with a semicolon.
I've made a typo in here so it should be inserted into code.
Come on him use what this would do.
This would insert a code into the table.
And what the application does is when the demo application launches up because the implementer come
in and render this run that would launch.
And this would get the code at the ID 10000 one.
Let's send this to a new field.
Not new field I would want to use.
You look at your bill.
I would want to call this code over here.
I would want to use a logger the way I can get it all get created is a very simple way to private log
will use SLA for lager lager lager.
It's the to of the factory or get longer for this specific class or import import lager.
I would want to use Othella Fujii in that so we have the Laga present now.
So I would use the lager dog.
This dog and talk log.
It's augured info.
You can log the details of the course come up.
So it would have been called Details called ten thousand one needs.
This I can launch this application now to check that everything's working fine.
When I launched the application up I get an error.
It says application failed the stack because field repository requests a bean of this type that could
not be found.
A been not found error.
What would you do when you get a B not found error in spring.
You need to check which been to of course deposit Rubinius not fun.
Why is this not fun.
Think about it this is putting.
And actually I missed the annotation repository.
So let's import that in depositary annotation.
And now let's launch it again.
If you're not really an expert at pring I would really recommend you to look at the appendix.
There's a indirection displaying which would really help you to understand spring and all these concepts
for the wedding.
Now let's continue with what we are doing with the specific entity.
Now you would see that there is a code in 2001 that printed here and it's printing the court or here
in this I would want to actually print the details of the code.
How do we do that.
Think about that too.
I would want to preprinted details of the code I would create to string at the right mix or generate
generate two string rightly generated to string.
I don't need the idea I just need the name to just say name and remove everything.
I just customize this so that this is very concise.
Of course with the name is printed.
Let's stop the application.
Run it again.
Cool.
Now think 10000 one is called G.P.A. in strip so it's getting the data from the database and printing
it.
Ok that's cool.
That's a lot of things that we have and we have created an entity we have created a repository we have
created a command line run.
There's a lot of things that are happening in the background.
What we'll do is for the next couple of steps we'll take a pause and revise what we have done and you
know we would look at what is happening in the background we'll turn a few switches on so that you would
get more log.
And we have more visibility into what's happening in the background.
Until then I.