Welcome back.
Now that we have a simple entity working this is the best time to play around.
And also to understand what's happening in the bag in this step what we'll do is we'll turn on a few
things.
One of the things is we are using which to the database so that's an in memory database and we would
want to see what the days present in there.
So we would need to turn to control on so that we can look at what the data in the background.
The other thing is we want to find out what the Kuwaitis Hibernate is generating what is happening in
the background with highborn.
So we'll turn on something called hibernates statistics and also we will print all the queries which
are being fired in the log.
Let's get started with doning the hitch to control on how we get down to control on spring door to door
control door enable user code to do that as simple as that.
This would enable to control when we launched we launched up next or this would be enabling her to control
next what we want to do is we would want to learn statistics.
So how do I turn hibernates statistics on.
I would want to see what's happening in the background with hibernated would want to see statistics
on it.
Is it spring.
JP You don't want to configure a property for the JPA so properties Dorte we get into the custom field
so I would want to configure the hibernate property and what we want to do is hibernate got generate
steady sticks is equal to.
This would help us generate a lot of statistics on how many queries are fired what's happening in the
background and all that kind of stuff.
In addition I would want to set the logging level for one of the specific packages that are not hibernate.
Just this package which is in hibernate which is dispensable for statistics Alt-A say the logging level
for this to debug.
The next thing I would want to do show all queries show all queries.
So I would want to see what queries are being fired.
So I'll just bring dot G.P.A. dot Sure.
Q Well is equal to.
This is good because this withdrawal all decrease.
However what I would also want to do is I would want to see what Bajrami does being say to these queries.
We want the courts ten thousand one so ten thousand one is a bad rap meet it if I want to be able to
see what parameters are being sent into this this would enable the debug logging for this package.
This is the package which is used when setting paramita.
So and the last thing I would want to also make sure is I would want to be able to format the queries
by default the queries which are printed are not formatted.
What we want to do is format the queries as well.
This is a hibernate property.
So the way we do that is format and usko.
Q Is equal to when or where you would want to customize something related to hibernate or that you need
to do is to paint that G.P.A. properties do it.
So let's get started with that in the application.
Let's see what would happen.
Let's stop the application and keep forgetting.
You'd see a lot of things that are printed in the console what we'll do is we'll take it step by step
and see what's happening.
So one of the first things which is happening is a biblical code is being the springboard has this feature
called auto configuration when springboards sees that there is an embedded database being used to it
in a database so Springboro cease OK this guy is using it in a database.
So I would want hibernate to create this key for me.
So it would turn something called create Kema on.
So what would happen is hibernate would look at the different entities which are present in there and
create this key for them create all the tables that are needed.
So that's how the table is being created.
The table is being created because of springboard auto configuration Springboro the configuration enables
the schema create and hibernate would create that schema for us.
So that's number one.
Next thing you would see is the execution of the sequel.
So what we have done earlier is created a file called data that sequel with a few ladies when spring
would seize a date or rescue will then that get executed.
That's what you see next in here.
So you'll see that the queries which are present in the data are not at school are being executed.
The thing is you did a school script from your date or the sequel that calls or whatever code we have
in there would be created mixed what we have is that right we clear the command line in which we are
running a query.
What we are doing is get the details of course.
So the query which is being fired is select the ID name from cord's where Id is equal to this.
What is the ID that is being sent am unable to see the ID that is being sent.
Lets look at it a little later for you know.
You can also see that there are metrics being put into it saying I've spent this much time preparing
the JTB statements excluding DJT with his statements and a lot of statistics that are being printed
for now.
These are the two one two that are important for us so the queries being fired and how much time its
taking for that school and B that they called 10000 1 which is what we put into the dialogue.
When did you hear that call.
Right.
So what is happening is this is being created.
The data is being populated.
However one thing that concerns me is the fact that de-value which is passed here is not being printed.
Lets look at why its not happening.
I go to the application of our properties.
So we said logging level or hibernate type is equal to debug.
Actually I made a mistake.
It should have been.
Chris you have to say the hibernate type 2 3 is to be able to see the values that are being assigned
to the bed and we do.
Lets go that off of the application started again.
Cool.
Now if you see that cause the and what is the tape.
So its saying OK this is ten thousand one thats good.
So by adding paramita one begin 10000 one.
Now I am able to see even the parameter values.
I'm able to see a decision matrix which are being printed in here.
How many queries are fired how many caches and other stuff which we'll talk about a little later but
for now what we have is good application.
So we are able to file a query.
We are able to see what's happening in the background.
And that's really good.
One of the things which will focus on doing this cause is not just trying to understand how to do something
with JPK but also trying to understand what's happening in the background.
So we look at the statistics and look at the general Greeley's and all that stuff.
And in this step we set that up.
So congratulations and I'll see you in the next step.