Step we revised our understanding of what's happening in the background in the step we would want to
write a simple unit test.
So we defined a simple method to be able to find a course in the course repository.
It's just a very simple method.
What we would want to be able to write a unit test to this and check whether it's working fine.
So that's what we should be focusing on in this step.
One of the things which we miss to doing in the previous step was to look at the histo controlling the
application of that property.
We've done statistics on really good then we don't queries on them being able to control on what we
didn't look at it yet.
So let's get to the hitch do control enough go to the browser and type in localhost ADHD flash hits
to control to this that you are a local host ADHD slashes to control going there.
You can see the values which you'd need to populate on your screen right.
No.
So your driver classes are headed to right where you are to busy you are.
Here's the one thing which you need to know in detail should be JTB Seacole unhitched do.
Colin mehm coal industry the user name and password is empty and you can take it once you do connect.
You'll be able to see the core stable which is present in here.
This is what the school has to control.
Once you select a table and run you can see the data which is present in for another to very simple
table like we have an ID name but this console would be using it extensively through the scores.
This is not just select queries if you want the insert date or the date and things like that.
You can do that from here as well.
So this is very similar to your database Klein fields article for example.
You may be using something like a skill developer or taught.
This is exactly the same except for the fact that this is on line.
This is a web browser kind of thing.
This is available as long as your application is available as long as your application is running.
You have all the tables and the database available for you when the application goes down the hatch
to cancel also goes down along.
Now let's shift our attention to what we want to do in this step which is to create a unique test for
our cause repository.
What we'll do is we'll create a class called depositary death and in all this find by ID and see if
the code which is returned back has the name that we wanted.
The most important thing that you need to understand is the fact that your desk board should be separate
from your source code.
So this is your production code.
So its main job is your production code.
Its main job at the source is your production configuration.
The source inside source says Java will not be part of the operation.
But this is more to test your code.
Either way create a unit test.
What I lose.
I'll start with copying them supplications just so I copy them all applications test and paste it out
and I renamed this s cause the pause.
The first thing I would do is to change the package name to back his name.
We should match the package name of the class that is being tested.
We want the best course repositories because repositories in the package Dawk repository Soldat repository.
That is the package we had.
I would want to put this control one command one move now be inside that packet.
Of course depositary test.
That's cool if you see this specific test.
The most important thing they do in addition to the OP I'd want to launch a spring context in my unit
test in these kind of situations we use something called at a with spring mode or class.
So I can mid-spring another class is used to write luncher spring Quantic the spring contex that we
would want to launch.
Is this bringing boot test so we would want to launch the entire spring boot context which is present
in here.
We would want to launch the entire more application Quon text which you have in here so that at Spring
boot best over here I can even explicitly specify the springboard context file that I would want to
launch.
I can take classes is equal to the more application class.
What I would want to launch is this demo application that.
This is the one which contains springboard application.
This is the context that I would want to launch and I'm spacefaring databasing flatus is equal to the
application that.
What this would do is it would launch up the entire.
So if I do a right click Puranas do this it would launch the entire context.
And because this unit test immediately within the context as well what would happen is first it is launching
the springboard context Plunger's this being good context.
We have seen what are the things that would happen at the launch of the context right.
The first thing is we hibernate created the table for us because it's enabled by supplying good configuration
then it would run the sequel files that would create the data that we would need.
It would fire the query also like the application class also has either.
So if you look at the application class this also runs the query which is pleasant to me.
So it runs the query and then what it would do it's a good run.
Whatever code that we write in just in the example we don't have any code in the test so you can see
that totally positive test is being done here.
We don't really have anything in the test right now so nothing will happen because of the test and then
the table would be dropped and the whole context would be killed.
So what would happen when I launched it just as the context has launched and the context is good.
For example let's say I would want to log something in here I go to the application and copy the logger
stuff so that I will be able to log things in here.
I copied the log or I would do is log the dot info.
I'll say d'Este is running contex lot.
Run the unit just like you Cronin's Jane.
Or you can select it from here.
You would see that the whole thing happens again.
The table created data is populated the queries run and as soon as the queries run the context is launched
then what would happen is your desk gets fired.
You can see here.
Testing isn't running.
Testing is running.
What do I mean.
I actually wanted to pipe into this morning that it does not really matter.
You can see that the what is in there is being printed in here.
And once the test runs it would actually drop the entire schema.
The sequence of events is very simple.
Context gets launched.
The restaurant and the context get killed.
What do we want to do here is we would want a desk because we pause it really.
So what we want the best is of course we pause the dirty and report it.
Let's create an instance for it in here and said this is going to be auto wired and the top is import
control shift or command shift to.
And now in the test I can call whatever I would want to call a positive 3.5 and by a D.
And I would want to pass in the ID of ten thousand one and I would get the court back same statement
to your local court is it could.
That's cool.
Right now I can write an essay on the code so I can say is it equals.
What's the name of the course.
Course not good.
What should be the name of because we don't get it from.
I can go to that are equal whatever name you have put it in here should be the name we should come back
to that EPS.
Let's get here and put it in and I'll look and one command one and add a static import for that as well.
So now you see that I'm asserting things with that that equals the left side is the expected value and
is the action.
And make sure that this is added to when you added to the unit messages which come up with much much
more helpful.
There's no longer testing a context Lord is just testing testing to find him.
So I call this find be a very basic test is to say that this is the most basic This is defined by the
method.
And now I can do it I click around as to just table it's created.
What does it test do.
The test also fired the test fired the query again.
You can see that because the positive test is in here because depositary test fired the query because
we are calling the repository method defined by ID or the ID that is being passed 10000 to one you can
see that the session metrics are being printed and the entire thing comes out.
I would recommend you to play around with this unit.
So you can change this to GAAP in 50 steps.
Let's say I would want to change it and say Gippi 800 steps what would happen.
Brantly.
And with this test would fail obviously because the name that comes from your database is Jaypee in
50 states.
What I'm saying I'm expecting to be in 100 steps.
So you would see that the test would fail.
You'd see that it says OK Janet companies and failure.
I'm expecting JP hundred dips but it was GP in 50 steps.
Janet it's also very helpful in saying what's the difference.
Inside the inside the brackets easten and fighting this dent here it's 1 0 here it's five.
That's the difference.
So this is where Juna just really helpful.
It would be able to automate can you find out any flaws in your code.
So if this find babies getting it wrong ID back out the wrong code.
Back then we would be able to easily find it out because these gene it would be running in continuous
integration.
This would be running as part of your bill so if and whenever there's a bug in your code this would
easily find it out.
Let's fix this.
Let's go back to G.P.A. in 50 steps.
If you run this you'll see that the test would succeed.
If this is the first time your writings uniters there are a lot of things that you might be learning
for the first time.
What I would recommend you to do is to try and play around with this unit test again and again try and
write a simple unit test a couple of more tests around the scenario maybe populate some data in here
so you can populate a new quote in here and try and play around with it and see what would happen.
One of the things that we really believe in 28 and it is the best time to learn is when you have something
working so you have a unit test working.
You have depositary you have an entity now you can play around with it take a back up try and play it
and break it.
And that's the best way to learn until the next step.
Baba.