Welcome back in step what we'll do is we'll try a simple method to delete the course the method which
we don't write is probably quite deliberately long.
So that's the one which we would want to write.
How do we delete the course again into the manager comes to your rescue.
The easiest way to delete a course is by saying to the manager.
Rimu You're in THE However I would want to first be able to get the entity for this idea what I can
do is I can call defined by it.
So first I would get the entity mapped by that specific thing to go to court as a call to find Beatty
you got removed.
That's basically your code right to that top you will delete.
Of course I've not written it back.
We'll deal with it.
Right.
So it's E-M who got all that I need to do is get the code and see into the manager but what we'll do
is we'll try and delete this course at this startup.
So the more application what I'll do here is over here as soon as I print the quote I like to train.
So it depositary don't delete by 80 percent.
So what we're doing is application start up we we're deleting 10000 one.
And also what I'll do is add a little bit more data.
So in the data scale right now I just have one row let's add a few more rows so that I can see the other
one 1000 2003.
So that says Bring in 50 stript spring board in it.
You can have them make it a service call which or one you would like allow or make this.
Now I would want to actually launch the application I'm launching this one right click on my application.
Right click on your application.
One of the things you should be cautious from now on is because we would be writing unit tests and also
run the application in parallel.
You should be careful about what you are running.
So if you go in here you can see actually that these are the death.
So if you want to run the best then you can do this if I want to run the application itself to my application.
I would want to run the applications I am running the application of we would start by looking at the
log and then we would look at the console.
You can see that I'm getting exception saying no.
And the manager with actual transaction every liberal you are trying to manipulate data you're trying
to be more.
Of course what you are trying to remove it in a method which does not have any transaction around it.
What is this transaction.
Why do we need a transaction.
Don't worry about it.
We'll talk about transactions a lot more.
All that you need to know is the fact that splitting makes transaction management very very easy.
So the problem is that the deliberate ID is trying to branded.
Of course it's bank to make a change in the code details.
If you look at defined by ID it is just getting the details of the court so it does not have a problem
but the deliberate ID method what it's doing it's actually trying to remove a quarter trying to delete
because it's trying to make a change in data.
If you are trying to make a change in data you should do it within something called a transaction.
For example there are a sequence of steps.
Right.
So if I'm transferring some amount from my account to my friend's account there may be two steps right
first deduct the balance from my account and transfer the balance into my friend's account.
I want to make sure that both of these are successful.
The second step fails then I would want the first step to be the worst.
I don't want to be in a situation where a hundred rupees is removed from my account but it's not credited
to my friend's account.
I don't want to be shot by a hundred rupees or dollars or euros which I will guarantee you will do want
to use that for transaction management enabled us.
We have a DVD section on transaction management.
A little later spring really makes it easy to manage transactions all that you need to do with that
transaction.
I'm importing our spring from book transactional in here.
Later we will talk about the difference between GPL and displaying transactions as well.
For now I'm adding a transaction on the cost repository.
This would ensure that any change that is done in the method that is present in the course depositary
any public method this would act as the start and the end of the transaction.
And that I think would be running in a single transaction.
So if anything fails everything that is changed as part of this method will be rolled back.
Never on this application.
The application started up fine right now.
So let's see what queery was the last one fine.
You can see that the delete query was fact delete from courseware IDs equal to what is the ID that was
sent dentals and 1 and it says that there were specific amount of time was spent executing that statement.
That's all right.
So first what it does it raises set the course and then we are trying to do that to Courtrai to find
by.
This is your de-select And then this executes the delete.
Let's see the data.
It's a fresher browser has can truly connect again.
Let's go to the code run.
You can see that ten thousand one is no longer there because that delete it in the step until now.
What we have done is very simple method be executed that from our application next what we would want
to do is we would want to write a unit test for that in the next step.
Let's work on that until then.
But.