Come back in this step let's write a unit test for the delete by the method.
What are the things which we did earlier is to call the pause read or delete by ID in the Application
class.
Actually it's not good to keep more defend it in here so I'll delete this from here so I'm deleting
the delete method in here.
So the data would be as it is which is present in the data or sequel.
All the doors would be present when we execute the unit test.
So now I would go and write dimeter for delete.
So I'm copying the method for find bady what I would want to do is delete the basic so delete by ID.
I would want to delete.
Bye.
So let's do that delete by 80.
Once you delete the row of 10000 one bullet youth 10000.
So if I am deleting 10000 do what should be the consequence.
How can I test it.
What would this do.
This would delete the row from the database so this is this will delete the code with an ID ten 10000
two from the database.
How can I check whether it's a work or not.
How can I write the unit for that I can check it by trying to retrieve data value back and seeing that
it isn't.
I'll take the first read or find by the OneTel ten doesn't doesn't.
I would check that it's not.
So I would want to check that this is not how they do that.
Said not generate as a signal method which would be helpful in checking whether something is not.
So if you have an error on the third then just do control one or command one and do a static import
of it.
So what we're doing in here is very simple.
We started with deleting delete which was done in here so it didn't matter it was deleting the.
So I removed the delete from there.
I don't want to actually write a unit test for it right now so I going to lead by the basic method we
call delete and check that that particular thing does not exist.
So let's run this.
Right click and as gene test you can see that the unit test has succeeded.
That's cool.
And now when I go to the log I can see that the delete queries file to the delete query is fired with
the idea that it doesn't do and then the Select queries fired the query does not come back with any
details as such.
So it does not come back with any details.
So what happens.
It would come back arsenal and the unit test would exceed one of the important things about this particular
unit test.
Is this unit test changing the date which is present when we write unit tests.
You would want to leave the state of the application as it was before running that you would need first.
So because this is modifying the state of the system state of the data that we are having.
What I would need to do is would need to put an end iteration called Doherty's context.
So I just need to say Dodi's context and import it in.
What would happen is after this test is one spring would automatically set the date up after the test
is run.
Spring would reset the data so that for the other deaths the data has not changed at all.
Think about this scenario.
Let's say I am getting the value of ten thousand two in here.
Let's say the name here we are checking for is the name put 10 dollars into.
If this test deletes that data and this test is dependent on that date to be available this test would
fail.
Even though there is no problem with the code what is happening is this this is deleting that data.
This test is not able to find it.
That's not a good situation to be in with your unit.
This is the reason why we need to put an end to these contacts.
What you said would exude this test.
It would make sure that everything is fine.
OK delete is working fine and it would reset the data to whatever it was before this test and that would
ensure that this system is in a consistent state for the this as well.
In this step what we did is we order simple unit test to be able to delete 10 doesn't do and we check
that after deleting the didn't doesn't do does not exist until the next step.
Boy.