Well come back in this step what we'll do is we'll create the same method.
The thing is with the same method we would want to be able to insert and did data as well so we would
want to be able to insert and update data using the same instead.
So how do I find if it's an insert or update.
If course Daut get ID.
ID is null then it means I would want to insert the row.
So here I would want to do instead.
Else I would want to do that.
So that's basically what we would want to do.
So if the code ID is null then I would want to do it insert.
Else I would want to do it.
So how do I insert with an entity manager.
It's very simple.
And the manager puts this this is the method I would want to use assist because if of course ID is not
null then what I would need to do is I would want to do entity manager dot merge merge Cox.
Once it's done I would want to be able to return to court very simple method.
There's nothing complex in it in here.
So all that we do is if it goes out get ideas and then we would want to insert into the code else we
would want more because we would want to save the details.
That's basically what we need to do.
Now what I'll do is I'll save a new course.
I would want to use the command line right now which we create a demo application over here.
Let's do this.
So I would want to create a new code depositary dot so I would say repository save and create a new
course new course and I'll give it a name.
Let's say microcell recess in hundreds.
You can kill the application if it's already there.
Let's leave it there.
No it's not here.
So let's run the application again.
So at the start of the day my application what we are doing is we are inserting a new course.
And we would want to check that it's working fine.
Cool.
So you can see here that Dean said Gridley's file insert into code name ID values and what are the values
which are sent in it turning in Microsoft is says in hundred steps and the ID which is sent in is one
Abnett called a sequence.
So what we have is inside the code we said this is the generated value when we say it generated value
what hibernate does it uses the default of creating a sequence to hibernate create a sequence using
the sequence to find the next value for the ID.
So it first called the sequence it get the value back.
So it uses that ID to insert the code in.
Now I can go to the H2 control and see the data as well.
Let's do that right now to control panic.
You can see that Mike.
So is this In hundred steps.
Is present in here with an ID of 1.
So you can play and play around.
You can insert more rules into this table and play and play around to see if the insert is working fine.
So in this step what we did was we tried and created a same method and b I was successfully able to
insert a new chord in.