Will come back if this is the first time you're writing unit tests.
I think that we are doing in here with course repository test might be seemingly fairly complex to you.
You might not be able to clearly understand what we are doing in here.
It might be really making you feel uncomfortable and that's fine.
Actually the most important thing is NEED TO seen is a very very important skill as we move on unit
testing would become a key differentiator between a bad programmer and a good programmer.
And that's why we make extensive use of unit testing in our courses.
It's not a problem if you're feeling uncomfortable with unit testing right now.
What I would show to you is that by the end of this course you'd be really familiar with human testing
how to do this and what are the different complexities that are associated with rating units.
So just hang in there and play around with the test.
If the unit does seem a little complex for you at this point don't worry what are we are writing in
the unit test.
You can alter it right into the application so you can go here in the demo application try doing the
same thing in here and see the change to reflect in the hatch to control.
So when you run the application you would see that that specific change would be appearing in your head
to control when you run the query select start from code in the hitch to control what would happen.
The change that you are making would appear so try and use that to try and get familiar so you can brand
play around.
Jinyan been trying to play around with the data better understand what's happening.
And in the meanwhile or the period of course you'd get familiar with the unit testing and the whole
thing.
The thing which I really believe in is the fact that if you are uncomfortable at something good hundred
times and then you really become comfortable with it.
OK let's end demotivation stuff in here and get back to what we are doing what we would want to do is
we would want to write a unit test for this method right.
So in a previous step we wrote the same method.
So the same method is going to change the data so it would know the context.
So I'll use the same thing as earlier so delayed by I didn't know I would want to do save what we would
want to do is called depositary Dotsie the details of the was the way we created the Save method is
that it is going to be able to handle both insert and the update so the ID is null then it will try
to insert.
Else it tries to avoid it.
So in the unit test what we'll do is we'll try and test the blade scenario.
So what I'll do I'll get a quote and update the details of it.
And check out.
So let's first get because so I use this cause it's all fine by the ten thousand one I have a cause
details first.
I can check what is the name of the cause right the name of the code.
At this point it should be JP In these steps.
That's cool.
So we got a course that's done now I would want to update the details of the course.
So how do I update the details of the code course dark set nime.
Let's say Tippee in 50 steps.
Did and I would want to call the depositary that see of course before I am able to take de-value I would
want to be able to update that too.
Now that the update is done now I would want to check the name of the court.
I would want to do a word get name again and check people so they could start and get it again from
the database so of course one Altaic one that name it should be J-P in steps.
They did what we're doing here is very simple right.
We are getting decors checking the details up because we are updating the details and we are doing a
Save and we are checking whether that standing fine to our left is very simple right.
And as the unit test that test is failing because actually I left last statement in here to remove that
statement.
So the test should actually look like this.
So of course save the change the details save the code and check the values fine.
Right.
Run as you notice.
You'll see that the test is succeeding.
That's cool.
That's very good.
Always good to see you.
But let's see what is happening in the test what is happening in the test.
Is first de-select queries getting fired.
So where is getting fire to retrieve the details.
And you can see that the idea which is going in instant a one right after that we are checking the detail.
So you're saying DPN 50 steps.
Abby did that.
Cool.
Now we are fighting an update query to be able to update the details of the cause.
And then what happens is a select query gets fired again because we are trying to get the details of
the call again from the database base and we are actually extracting didn't you value from the database.
So that's pretty good.
Be able to see that that succeeding in the step what we did is we wrote a test for the U.S. from it
that we don't test for the update scenario.
So we do because from the database the abated the value of the name of the course.
And we checked with that being the property until the next day.