Welcome back this step let's quickly review all that we have done in the last few steps.
We started creating a simple implication using spring in laser and then we created an entity called
CTS and then we created a code repository to be able to insert a bit delete and do operations do the
typical KRAD operations on the court because repository helps us to do that.
And we created a simple unit test cause reports that retest and the cause depositary two-Test uniters
the different method which are present in the court repository.
So if I look at the court the important things that are present are declaring a primary he called a
primary key will uniquely identify each row in a table.
So if I said ten thousand one there will be only one row in that table with ten thousand one.
If I said ten thousand twenty five they'll only be one at a maximum.
There will be only one row with that primary key and we find a column called name.
So this court's table has two columns ID in name and we created a few All-Met that would be created
getters and setters.
We created a constructor.
This is something JP needs.
So those are the things that we established in our entity entity is a court.
So typically if we start the entity this causes like any Jawa bean How do you make the beans special.
How do you make to be an entity by adding an entity an entity is a bean plus plus.
So a being that is told to the database which gets the values from the database that your entity.
This actually maps to row in your table.
So an entity been mapped to row in the table.
So there's a row in the table which is responding to these bean.
That is what is an entity.
And then we went to the cause repository we use entity manager find method to be able to find a specific
ID.
So I'm able to find a specific row of our course by using its primary key.
And then we were able to write a method to delete by ID as well.
So we use the ID to delete a row and we wrote a method to be able to save the details by saved we mean
both insert and update in the IDs null.
Are trying to answer it in other ways.
We are able.
We are trying to see the details.
We are trying blabby the rule and in the course reports retest widowed corresponding you'll notice that
the details of ten thousand one and saw that the name of the cause is expected.
We deleted 10000 two and saw that the value when we are leaving find by it and doesn't do is null.
So the rule is deleted one of the things is we don't want uniters to change data.
We do are at the end of the unit test we would want to actually reset the system back to the same data
and that we achieve by using a dirties contacts so that ensures that any other test makes you that it
doesn't do the role it's still there in the database.
So this unit test would run it would check all the things that we do want to check.
And after that the data gets reset again that's done by using the Doherty's context annotation.
And we wrote a simple save unit test as well.
We took the code we are Bladud the name of the code and we saw that when we retrieve because again we
get the updated details back and this what we did until now is indeed the application.
We use something called the command line.
So what would happen is whenever the application gets launched we know what these contacts get to launch
whatever is in the method gets executed.
So in here as if no we are actually creating a very simple new course if you would want to play around.
This is the place you can try and play around too.
You can call any repository that's in here and go to the hash to control and see if they are reflecting
or not.
When you launch up the hash to control and look at the data for the court you'd be able to see all the
details that we have changed as by of offer one.
One more thing I would recommend you to do to get for that understanding of what's happening behind
the screen is to use the debug mode.
So if I'm running the demo application let's kill this and putting the button point in here.
Double clicked on here and you'd be able to enter to the point and I can come here and now I can tell
right click debug as a job application or that we had to do was come to my application at a debug point
in here and then actually it's called a break point or at a break point in here by double clicking in
there and I click debug as job application.
Typically we use it on us in this situation we are using a debug as now launches it up in debug perspective.
So now I can say yes and you see that we are inside the debug perspective in say D-CT minute.
If I go to the database now go to histo control know and refresh the page kind of again.
And go to the court and you'll see that the new code is not yet inserted.
You can see that the new code is going to be inserted a little later.
Now a piece of code for now what we're trying to do is retrieve the details.
Put those in one way you can is good.
This is by using your function keys.
Or you can use the keys which are present in here.
So I would want to step over FCX.
So not the details of the course I retrieve.
You can see what's happening in the log.
I do a step over again you would see that the details of the course up in did had become so again.
And now I would like to add this statement again.
You see now that the ROI is getting inserted into it I gets called you can see what I will use that
I get.
But as you can see these statistics which are getting fired and I can go here run and I can now see
that it's having neuropathies and because that's inserted in and also go ahead and go do a F-8 function.
Afraid that would complete the execution.
Now I can actually go and see all the data which would just present in here.
It would all the data that is present at the launch.
So this is one of the other things you can do to be able to understand the whole thing.
For that this is called debugging.
We're actually putting a debug point in the application in debug mode and checking everything is working
fine in the step we wanted to give you a quick overview of what we have done until now as well as show
you a few tips about debugging and then the next step book.