Welcome back one of the most important concepts behind JP is this thing called an entity manage it in
this and a series of next couple of steps we would look at NTT manager in detail.
We'll try and understand all the background details about the entity manager to be able to understand
the manager in depth.
What we do is we create a simple playground method call this public wide play with the manager.
I couldn't find a better name than that because there are a lot of things I would want to play with
related to the entity manager.
So let's use that name.
I'm creating this in the course repository.
And what I would want to do is I would want to be able to.
This is the de-bug.
So I would need the debug thing which is running in the background because depositary test actually
start with a simple test.
It's just a very simple test.
And just call this play with entity manager I swear.
And over here what we would want to do is just to get off the method which is present in the supposedly
all that we want to do is play with entertainment minute that depositary taught want this stuff we don't
need all this I would just want to get play with it and manage it play with the manager because it was
a test would call the code repository method play with an entity manager and log word or debug it in
full.
OK I don't have a lot going on here.
So it's pull out the logger from here just so that we are very clear of what's happening where I pulled
out the logger and let's say lovebird in full we are to you.
Play with it.
Did he manage it.
But OK I guess we have all set up that is needed.
Let's run this.
What will happen is the application contacts get Sloan.
So the scheme is created the data is inserted and you can see that the within 15 minutes start is triggered
here.
So that's good.
So we now have the team manager play with the manager at methedrine he said.
Now let's start playing with them to the manager what I would want to start off by creating a simple
call and saving it.
So I would want to say entity manager dart assist Sainty manager that person is used to create a new
thing.
So if you want to create a new entity that's dispersement that adds a new course of what is what you
would want to do.
So let's say the new cars that I would want to create is verb's services in steps.
So as we saw earlier this would create a euro.
So it would create a ticket to insert query and instead that through into the database.
Now inside of this what I would want to do is take a step further I shift.
I'll dig this into a local variable I'll call this course I'm setting a new name for this I'll say start
said name.
So he's got 100 steps updated vild this update be saved.
So what would happen.
Let's try and run.
So not this actually have to run the course repository just like chronicity and it does.
Let's see what Lobban to consume.
Just accept that.
I would definitely know.
But would the update be fired.
So the is inserted.
What is the details that are inserted into the code.
So within a hundred steps that's pretty cool.
And you can see that here there is also an update code name to call to question mark with a question
mark.
So it's also updating the new value that I have set it into the name into the database.
So what's happening in the background is when I run this when this method is called first.
This is getting inserted and then this rule is getting saved to the database as well.
But I'm not really requested to save this.
How is this data getting saved.
One of the important things is the transactional annotation.
So this and that method is in a single transaction and while we are within the scope of a transaction
entity manage it keeps track of all the things that were inserted through it that were updated with
whatever things were mortified through it.
And the manager would start keeping track of them.
In this example the course is something which is being inserted through the into the main page.
So whatever changes I make to decors are kept track of by the entity manager.
I don't really need to say did the manager or dot merge this to save the details.
What the manager does is it would keep track of all the things that managed through it in here.
And whenever there's a change on it it would make sure that that changes as the state did the database.
Let's do one thing.
Let's actually call the repository directly with the manager in our launch of the application.
So I'll do a window prospect to open perspective job.
So I'll go back to our perspective.
I'll open up the day on one application class and what I would want to do is not really do all the stuff
in here right now.
So let's not need all this stuff.
All that I would want to do is play with entertainment riposted or play with the manager.
That's the only thing which is called From the day my application right now.
That's everything.
And to be the implication again.
So what we are doing in the play with the manager as of now is clearly in your goals and setting and
Neme and we saw that when we were running the unit there was a query which was fired to get the update
then.
But now I would want to actually show you the same thing in the database go back to the history control
continue.
On its Web services in hundred scripts.
So what are what changes which we are doing in here are actually reflected down to the database.
Okay.
So that lesson number one on NTD manage it.
So if you were actually in say the track thats lesson number one about NTT manager I know you are inside
the transaction and you are managing something with the entity manager when you are updating something
or deleting something or you inserting something in that particular thing continues to be managed by
the entity manager until the end of the transaction to be called here.
Even though I only saved it here what I would change is you are doing two because later in the transaction
are also being tracked by the entity manager and they are also assisted.
So if I do or said name something after that as well.
Then the manager keeps track of those changes and says them we'll talk a lot more about the manager
in the next step on the line.
But by.