We'll come back in the previous step.
We saw that in the manager within a transaction keeps track of all the things that Adam managed it.
So when you call into the manager or entity manager or merge you are in agreement on a specific object
when a specific entity.
What are the changes that are done to that entity in the rest of the transaction are all sort of tracked
by the entity manage it and the state to the database.
Let's look at another example.
So courses there to create a quartz one.
This is of course one called two and the two in in the quarter to quarter one and let's create a new
one called two and that this code through.
And of course 2.70 that's cool.
Right now this code is but this did by the manager.
And this one is octopus's had been into the manager.
Let's give it a different name.
So it's no longer there.
So Weezer's Let's call this angle Jesus and Oh here we are actually setting and logis in 100 steps.
Updated you know what would happen when this gets started again.
It's the courts when details get saved and the courts do the deal.
Also get to the well.
So is this an hundred steps and allergies in a hundred steps.
So that's what you would see.
You can start BBDO here and run the application and see what would happen if you manage it also has
a method called flush into the manager to flush what entity manager that flush does it.
The changes which are done until then they would be sent out to the database so I can call into the
manager at plush and multiple places so that the changes up to that point are sent out of the database.
So now you can see this basic transaction as four steps right.
So the first step is creating the code.
Then we get a bidding because one actually to be accurate in quarter one and abrading quotes.
And we are creating calls and upgrading calls to let's say I don't want the calls to change just to
be going to the database.
So after this stage I don't want all the calls to data details to go to the database at all.
How can I do that.
There's another method in the manager.
So let's say in city manager Darren Deedat cost.
So what would happen after this is the changes to course to are no longer tracked by the entity manager.
So what you would see that goes to that set name will not be executed if they kill the application and
start again and go to the H-2 control.
You see that the because to name remains that Anglo is in handed steps Kitchener's started up you would
see that the debate which is done did the courts do which was Ankiel just in a hundred steps are not
being saved because after the document that is called on us Pacificare entity that entity is no longer
tracked by the entity manager.
Let's say I am creating the courses first let's say I move this stuff also or don't support someone
not to name the objects.
The courses I'm actually moving them a little down.
I also remove the flash in here so that we kind of treat this as two steps right.
The first step is creation of all the cards that flush it.
So they are sent to the database and then I'm detaching only chords to for now.
So what would happen if you ran it only close to his detection.
So one name would be said to webservices in hundred steps.
Updated Howard-Costello name will not be updated because ghost 2 is not tracked by the entity manager
anymore.
If I wanted to do that one then I can do this as well.
So the manager don't detach.
Of course one could find that if you ran this application and see the stock until you would see that
the date would be as it is here.
So it would be web services a hundred steps and ledges in hundred steps.
These updates will not be saved to the database because those entities are not backed by the entity
manager at all.
The other way of not tracking entities is by clearing everything out to ensure of calling Dadge on everything.
You can also say the manager not clear.
So this would clear everything that is there in the entity manager so it would clear out everything
that is being practised by the manager and everything including quotes when calls to will not be tracked
and whatever changes you make to them will not be flushed out will not be saved to the database.
Let's kill the application started again.
You'll see that the data in the database.
These two values the update will not be saved to it is refresh.
Can you please on.
So you can see the first two rows in here.
So within hundred trips and ledges in hundred steps the updates are not saved to the database.
So in this step we look at how you can have the manager not track a few entities.
So by default the manager tracks everything.
If you want to track a few entities you can tap into the demand or detach.
If you want to clear everything out you can call into the manager directly.
And then the next step for.