Really come back in the previous step we looked at the limiter and also we look at the detachment in
the step we would take a quick look at Dubery freshmen.
Third was just present in the NTD manager.
So in the previous example what we did is we created quoters flourished and we did clear.
So what happens here is the managers are clear.
So it clears all the things that managers.
So it's not managing anything at this point.
So what changes you make.
They are not reflected in the database.
Now let's set up for the next example for the refresh Let's remove the entity manager.
Clear method call it in here.
And we have a flush.
So I don't really need a flush in here.
So we basically have the insert here and the updates which are going on here.
So one of the things I would want to do now after doing the update.
Let's say these are done in different method.
These are not really done here.
So after doing the update say I would want to refresh course one with the details that are present in
the database.
So 12:45 I would want it to have the details that are as it is in the database.
I don't want the updated date for one to go through.
I would want to refresh code one with the contents from the database.
How they do that the way I can do that using the manager is by using entity manager fresh.
So what would happen is all the changes which I've done to quartersawn are lost and cost one will be
refreshed with the content that comes from the database.
So the steps are like this right so you create the code.
This when I do a flush.
These are inserted to the database so these two codes are being inserted to the database.
I'm trying to make changes.
These are still managed by the entity manager so into the manager keeps track of them.
And here I am saying to the manager that refresh code 1 what happens to one content alone the candidate
of course one alone would be refreshed and we would get the data from the database.
Let's see what would happen.
Let's put it the point in here I put a debug point in here.
It will do so.
And let's do it right click the bogus
I put a debug point in here.
I mean I would need to debug the application to add to it right like debuggers.
Joe it asking me if I would want to launch and DBA perspective and say yes and I would want to go inside
this method.
So I'll say function at five or you can take a step in which is present or you.
This is going in a little deeper than what I thought.
And since we already have a breakpoint at the start of the Course repository I would say continue our
step return to find.
Now.
The execution is at core.
So now let's see what would happen.
I would clear out the control two that I can follow what's happening in here.
Make this a little bigger.
And let's follow this closely enough.
The shortcut first step or is it.
So Alex the new code I think will happen with the database.
Now I'm posting it.
It's just calling for a sequence.
So as soon as that persists the manager is calling for a sequence and setting devaluing to decode.
So if you look at the code you can see that the idea of the cards is that what's the idea of the cards.
One that's the only thing which is that because it's not still save the data.
It is a sentence or two on function f six function F 6 now.
So the could do as well so of to get the ID do too.
I guess it should we do I guess this gets a value too.
So now we are calling flush What does flush flush close to save this data down to the database.
So what would happen.
So what did the flush do the flush inserted because in so inserting to cause it saving the details down
the database web services in hundred steps and inserting the code name ID values and lodges in hundred
steps into that as well.
So now duros are inserted down into the database.
Now lets get the next statement before that I would do everything from the control function f six sir
said name.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happens.
And now what does the data in court.
Of course when data is so is in hundred steps updated that the name.
But now I'm trying to get a fresh course.
What would happen.
Observe carefully.
Function FCX so you can see that the liquid is fired on quartersawn so you can see that the ascent is
of one which is the idea of decors one and the data for course when it's refreshed and you see that
it has a value.
So in a hundred steps and now I'm going up flush.
But even though I'm doing a flush now what would happen is the court one has decanting which is present
in the database.
So this does not need to be saved at all because this is exactly matching what the data is the thing
which needs to be saved between just decors to a function f 6 or the sent out update cause said name
musical to something where Id is equal to something which ID the ID which is sending is 2 and the Anglo
just called the second code is updated descript the name for that is updated and saved down to the database.
Now I can press function F-8 to complete the execution.
If you go to the hash to control now and see the data you would see that this change is lost.
So this change is not saved down to the database.
So if you look at the code so on it would have the name as well.
It is in hundred steps.
However the cost to the name as and lurgy is in a hundred steps.
So in this step what we did is we tried to understand did refresh method in detail.
What we also did is look at what's happening in the background for each of these steps.
I would recommend you to do a debug step with this to understand the whole thing much more.
I'll see you in the next step.