Welcome back in this step we'll try and replace all that we have learned about and manage it.
India-A manager is a symbol in the face.
It's an interface to something called persistent gone text.
So persistence context is a very important concept as far as GPA is concerned.
Here we are playing with a lot of entities.
One is an entity cause to an entity.
And there might be other entities we are playing with in a single transaction.
All the entities that are being saved through the entity manager are thieved to something called persistence
gone.
It's the persistence context keeps track of all the different entities which are changed during this
transaction.
And also it keeps track of all the changes that needs to be stored back to the database.
And we saw that in the manager of course a lot of different methods right.
It offers a lot of fine methods to be able to execute queries against the database and retrieve data
back.
It offers both this method so that I can save.
I can create an entity in the database and the manager MoJ method help me to save the changes that I
have done because down to the database we can delete an entity by using the Remove method.
We also Lubet the flush method which helps to persist all the changes until enough down to the database
in the middle of a transaction as well.
And also we look that refreshed method which helps us to override the changes and refresh the content
from the database.
We also have the detachment that we would detach the entity from the persistence context what happened
with the detachment that is that particular entity.
Changes to it are no longer tracked by the entity manager.
The manager is a very important thing for you to understand.
So I would recommend you to play around with the entity manager and also try and the different stuff
which is present inside the interface and the manager until the next step.