Welcome back.
We're all used to writing as well Kuwaiti's try to convey tolex data from God.
This is a school Kriti.
I can't wait to start from code.
We're letting name like birth and the age 100 steps so I can do things like this this run the query
and it would run and meet things which match that specific thing so it if you look at the query it select
start from code with name like percentage hundred steps within single quotes.
So this is a normal school query which we.
Right.
This is the start from court.
And here we are defining a very condition bad name like you're defending a condition or I can say where
either is equal to one.
This is only the first rule because it matches the idea one.
So this is normal.
Q However there is something called Jaypee.
Q This is Jaba persistent QAD language in.
Q Well what we do is we query from the database tables in J-P Q will be created from entities.
So this is from table.
This is from relationship if Will queries from where is Gilchrest queries from tables whereas JP Cuil
queries from entities What would you be.
Q Well queries that we write those are converted into as queries by the JPA implementation that is hibernate.
What we write would be JP queries which would be right using entities to read AJP queries using them.
And those are converted into Escuela queries.
Talking to the tables.
So typically we'll provide a way of writing queries using entities.
How do we write.
Well queries.
So for example select start from course later I want to do a query of this can select start from course
in JP.
This index will be very simple.
So select here instead of start.
I would need to do something else so from there I would want to weigh the From entity.
Here we are not talking about this table of course but we are actually talking about the entity the
entity which we have in here is of course that also having the same name as Kosilek start from course
as the name of the entity.
And I'm giving it to alias C.
Say.
C from CT that's the the you create just we just select start from code.
What we do in this step will write a few simple J-P queries and try and execute them.
So let's start with excluding this greatest legacy from what we lose we'll create a simple unit just
copy the cost repository that we have and I call this JP Cuil test and inside this would remove everything
else except for the first.
All the other stuff and all here would want to be able to execute a query instead of course repository
we would want to use entity manager and entity manager or I can just say.
And the I can execute crazy you don't create query.
That's the way you can actually create a query over here.
I can't pass in what we have written in here.
It's a legacy from code.
So this is the way you can create a query and you can execute the query.
I think that does not get this list and I will take this and store it to a new local variable.
This is returning a results back and let larget out larget dot info.
I'll put the query also just for the US to be able to search and it's returning what it's strict running
this value back what does that value.
I rarely use this sort of list.
Right.
So let's now run this unit test and see what it returns back remember.
And you can see that this is what it is printed on the log.
So it seeing all the things that we expected.
So I think web services in hundred steps and lodges in hundred steps updated the Nepean 50 steps and
all the other kind of stuff that present in here.
That's pretty cool right now.
We're able to create using the J-P Q And we will want to do a few more things with the JP Cuil that
tried a couple of more simple queries.
One of the things here is that I'm using a R-Type.
I'm not really using the fact that this query would return a call back.
How do I do that.
How can I get this greedy to say that I am going to return a call back.
I can use another parameter of course taught us.
So over here what we're doing is die.
So now when I actually let's create a local variable out of this.
So this is a query.
So when we create the query here we are actually using something called a table the query to type query.
Of course we are saying this is lightning a quarterback.
However if you look at this if I expect this to a local variable basing all that and say query this
is using a simple liquidy type.
Great is when I'm passing the pipe I'm saying this is the gradiently twigs.
And this is the kind of results that I expect back I expect results of type called Dark class.
Now when I get the results back I can add type argument as well so I can change type 2 list of course.
This is much better.
Right so this is better pipes I'm saying instead of just list and think this is a list of course type
queries are always better because they make it easy to read your program.
It makes it very clear what results you are expecting back.
So this is fine by A-type typed.
So here we are getting a paper created.
The other thing is just like the query we executed.
You can also use very conditions in here.
So below are a simple way or condition in here so find by id ups what Spike But actually let's just
say grvy basic art you can call this JP Cuil basic
and this is Jaypee.
Q typed and this is JP
an all here Sexta from CT.
Our condition within single rare name like per cent stips.
Now let's see what this would print.
This is from course where name like hundert these two courses are printed in the control of Web services
in hundred stirps and timbering Boudinot understood those two things which end with hundreds steps are
printed in so despicable as we talked earlier.
We are using entities in our future.
We will actually use the relationships as well.
Here we are just using entities.
When we define the relationship between cause and student what we'll do is we'll use that relationship
also to write create is using J-P kill for now all great is that we have written out very simple ones.
The next step bovver.