Welcome back in this and the subsequent steps we would start looking at some of the important annotations
which are provided by GPA and hibernate.
So we should be careful about using Hibernate annotations because when we use g.p one of the flexibilities
you get is you can easily shift from hibernate to any persistent provider or any other JPA implementation
like toppling Korder that.
But when you use the hibernate bespeak feature that means you are tied to hibernate.
So always remember that when you're using Hibernate will feature Let's now start with one of the first
annotations which is at the table.
What does it use up at table at table is used to define the name of the table.
You know what we're doing is we are mapping a code stable to code entity.
How would that be situations where this table is called something else.
This table might be called code details or something of that kind.
So in those kind of situations we can use the table with the name.
So for example I can't right now say the name of the table is called Details Howard the entity I would
want to store it in is course.
Now let's import the Jarek persistence table into the table in and I would stop and start the application
again.
You would see that the table which would be used would be called detail so the table annotation is used
to define the name of the.
But you can see that the application context fails just died because the data that sequel contains or
does it contain it contains cause it does not know about the details.
So let's look at the schema which is being created first.
You can see that the name of the table which is being created is called underscores the dangers the
court and the maps do courts underscore details table actually here we are seeing code details.
So it automatically changes that and creates course underscored the delays because typically when we
are creating tables the convention which is used is two separate word by underscores here.
Instead of course I would need to state code underscored details underscore details could the details
listed the application.
Now let's refresh our connection to hash to control and cause details.
You can see that the table name is now called Details ID name.
So even though inside our entities we call it code inside the table.
It is called details.
Also the other thing you would observe the fact that the queries and everything are now generated to
call underscore DDL so it's now select start from chord's underscored details it update course underscored
details.
So you'll see that the G.P.A. is actually doing a lot of magic.
So even when the entity and the table names are different when you doing something with the code the
updates are directly sent out to the court underscored details.
But the only thing that you would need to do is to map it you map it once and you can forget about it.
So the fact that your entity name is different from the table name you don't need to tell that in every
query in every repository and all that kind of stuff that you need to do is to link once to JPA using
the table and addition and that's it you can forget about it or that I'll go back.
I don't want to use cause details.
I would want to stick with codes so I would actually I could do either this or I can remove the annotation
completely and I would actually even with the changes which I present in here and restart it now you
would see that we are back to normal.
We would be using the Course table the table name is called We are inserting dating to court and this
would stop the court Dibon and let's refresh its color codes and give everything as expected as we had
earlier before this step if your name of the entity is different from the name of the table then you
can use the table annotation.
And in the next step by.