This step let's look at another important annotation call.
So at column I can't specify the name of the column.
So here I can say this name column is not really name it's old.
It's called name.
I can do something of that kind.
So what would happen.
The table in the column in the table this field maps do would be full named.
So whenever you update name the changes would be sent to a column named fullname.
Let's write that.
Let's change data sequel.
Here it should be Fullam because in the table it's fully if I stop and start the application and refresh
to see the code what does it have.
It has fully named the name of the column in the table is full Lim.
However the name of the field is different so in that case I can use the name is icle different name.
And what are the important attributes which represent in the column.
Let's look at them right now.
All of the important things that is present in column attribute is something called Lebel to label is
equal to.
That means name cannot have a null value.
So let's say I'm going to the unit test.
So let's go to the uniters that we have.
Relate it to the courts depositary to Wall Street it and we have a play written to the manager method
which is present in here which is being called from here.
So let's use that.
Now if in here let's say I'm sitting of course the data set name of this so let's clear all this stuff
out.
So I would commit all this stuff which is present in here.
I just leave this stuff which is related to course what so we're creating course when you're setting
the name of what to do.
Let's see what would happen.
What do you think will happen.
Police work from the unit test just doesn't it.
So play with it to the manager.
As you know as it continues to succeed that astonishes me how does it happen.
Let's go and look at it again.
The reason I think happened is we did not call it the his method on Quarterman So I would say persist
of course with because we did not call the police this matter and the manager is not really managing
the entity yet.
So that's the reason why it did not fail.
Now let's run that again.
You see that it's failing a database integrity violation exception.
Why is it failing.
Because now what we said is this is non nullable field.
This field cannot be null even if you look at the console and just go a little bit up and see the table
definition create table code.
It creates a table with a not null definition so this field cannot be null.
And if you look at it here it is data business school exception.
That is not allowed for this specific column.
So it's very good practice for you to specify things like this.
What this would prevent is bad data coming through.
So in your application you want the data quality to be a really really good.
So all the possible constraints that you have in your data.
It's good to set them using your column annotations to really get couple of them.
So we started with name and then we moved to nullable.
The other things which are present in them are what is unique.
Space.
If this is a unique value across the table this value will be unique.
For example feel like SSN.
Those kind of fields are unique.
So even though you don't want to use SSN as a primary key you can specify a unique constraint on that
specific field.
You can't say whether it's nullable whether it's insertable.
So whenever you say a column is insertable falls then whenever an insert is then whenever a new rule
is created in that table that column will not be sent.
So the Indians initial insert query that column will not be sent.
You have updateable available through to indicate if that column needs to be included in the update
statements that are sent.
So if you put updateable physical default then in all the update for that entity that particular column
will not be sent.
The other attributes which you can specify on the column and addition are lent.
So if it's a string field you can specify the maximum length so you can say this field is maximum 255
characters and things like that.
You can if it's a number of fields.
You can also specify scale and position in the step below that some of the important things related
to the add column and addition redefined a different name for this specific column.
And also we look at what happens when I have an infallible set to false.
And we also look at various different attributes that are allowed on top of this annotation.
What we'll do now is really quickly report all the changes that we have done.
So I don't want to use the I would want to leave the nullable as false in here.
That's cool but I don't want to name as a full name so I'll go ahead and change this and change this
as change that it will back.
So now you would have a proper running application.
And I see you on the next step.
All right.