It come back in a step we would look at some of the burden in addition to which are related to updating
and maybe some of the Times a few applications had the requirements that I would want to store when
the specific rule is updated last time and when this rule was inserted I would want to store the created
name of that particular role.
And also I would want to store the updated time of that particular in those kinds of situations.
Hibernate provides a solution.
Remember this is not a solution which is provided by GPA.
So this is more of a custom thing which is provided by hibernate.
So let's say I would want to start play it.
I would want to be able to store the app the did did.
Or it's called The Last Updated.
And I would also want to be able to store the he did it.
I'd want to start with the date and the time as well.
So in these kind of situations you would use something called Local date.
This is one of the things which is introduced by Java 8 earlier.
We were used to using Java dot dot dot but that's not really a good thing because it kind of represents
the time daytime and all that kind of stuff.
That's Wayne Jowler 8.
It was made much more clearer and there is something called quality time.
So he would want to store date and time.
That's what we are specifying by using this local date time and here local time created.
These are the two columns that we want to make use of.
However we need to tell hibernate that this is the last update date column.
So every time you make a change to this row this column needs to be updated with the date stamp.
How do I tell that you can say that is by using an annotation update time of day time stamp.
If you look at it as I said earlier it's hibernated.
And additionally to hibernate in addition not really AJP annotation.
So that's something you need to remember and the other in addition which is present in here is at created
time.
Now let me add that in the timestamp and decrease in time stamp on the last updated and that we did
that a couple of things that we would need to do before we are ready to test them.
The first thing is data are not equal right in the data or that sequel be only populating the ID and
the name are not properly to the created date and the did it so I need to populate this data is data
inserted into the data isn't.
This does not go through hibernate.
So we have to manually put the data in here.
Last updated the and it.
Let's put it down so that it's much more clearer.
And we did date last updated date read use and date last updated date.
That's good.
Now let's put the values in as well.
The values I would use this a state function.
So date for and it would populate the things as this team or whatever this estate was at that point
of execution of the query.
So that's good.
So the day that the insertion is now called right now what we want to do is if you look at the play
with the manager at this is call that startup of the application.
Right.
In our obligation what are we doing.
We are calling to play with them to the manager.
So all here let's create a course that we are already creating a court.
So what I'll do is I'll also get an existing cause and we abate something on it.
So what I do is I'll quote to instead of creating a new quote I'll get it from the database.
So we have fine by id met Ted in here.
So let's do that fine by ID.
And let's say cut and run and called Stu doc said he would want to set the name to ablated 2001 A thousand
one what's the code name.
It's DPN 50 steps.
Let's didn't name to that.
And now that stop and started the application and see what would happen.
All three of them anti-love is a couple of things I'd be different and the time stamp creation time
stamp.
And then we updated the data or that sequence with the new data for the state of New columns.
We put it as the default and then we went in on my application.
We were calling to play with them to the manager.
And over here we are seeing that be a new code.
So it's an homage to steps and also taking one of the existing courses deeply into the steps and we
are updating that description offered.
That's good.
Let's go to the database and see what's happening there.
This is the org which is created through the right this is the one web site within hundred seventy three
are into that thing.
So this is having a created date and the last update.
That's cool.
Not his own the creator did and last updated it.
And this is 10000 one thing which we updated.
So which we cord in the end the manager said the need to J-P in 50 steps updated.
So for this one you can see that the updated date is different from the created.
So for all the rest of the stuff that doesn't do that doesn't free the I did it and created it out are
the same.
So you can see that even including the millisecond they are same.
However for the other one because when we updated the row what happened the update the time stamp gets
updated this gets updated.
And this is different from the created times them.
You can also see the queries which are fired in.
So when we look at the queries which are fired in you'd see that when I'm sending the insert into cores
What is it doing it's sending created a lot of data date.
So he had to create a date and the last updated date for the website is in 100 steps close.
And when the Course is being updated it's created did the last update date and the name you can see
that the created date is being sent from whatever was there in the database.
The old value was picked up from the database and sent discreate it did.
But the new timestep.
So you can see that this is getting filed 15 20 20 182 right at the new one 15 21:30 180 is being sent
as updated timestep the old value of the row is being sent for.
Created what we look at is how to ensure that you create a date and the last updated date are automatically
populated for all the rows in your database.
This is done by using a couple of hibernate and additions at Abay time stamp and at.
Until the next step play.