Welcome back in the step we look at named query annotations.
So if you look at this specific thing we are actually hand-coding decree in.
So this means if I have to use it to use the query somebody else they will need to hardcoded again.
I would need to type in the entire area again named queries will help you to prevent that.
So with named queries you can assign a name to a query and use it.
So how do I create a named query.
It's very simple I can go to court for example this is the entity here right here I can add a Nemed
queries a named query about Ixtoc persistence and all here I can fake the name for a query that get
on course.
I would like to end it with a query query get all quotes this and comma you can specify the query set.
What's the query query we want to use.
Is this select see from quotes.
This becomes a named query and this can be used in other things.
Now I can use here instead of create query I can say create a named query to create named query using
what is to get all courses.
You get to create named query and it was created Get this.
So let's see what would happen if you run as a unit test.
I'm running all three tests.
OK.
So this once.
So you would see that the queries are properly run and you are getting the right details out.
This is selected from.
That's perfect.
It's getting all the details and it's printing all the details out here that's good so that unnamed
query where you'd see that.
Here we have another query that I would want to create a named query for this as well.
How can they do that.
And let's say I come here and say at named query name is it to create a Get hundred step code.
This let's call it that way.
And I would try and put the queries equal to the query which I copied.
Ha.
You can see that there is an error coming up saying duplicate an addition of a non-repeatable type named
query.
So this is not really a repeatable annotation.
So because of that what happens is I cannot do something of this kind.
What I would need to do is when I want to define multiple name queries I would need to use another.
In addition it is called named Kuwaiti's so jolly expose's since named queries.
And while we're here I can see value is equal to all here.
I have to define and write off named queries.
So name query come up under that name for it.
And this is how you would do a set of name queries.
So that is how you define multiple name queries.
This is not really any easy way of doing it.
So now I have defined this so I would want to use the named query here as well.
So let's do that create named query.
That's cool and that should run the unit as depicted in this league.
So it's a green but if you look at the queries you'll see that the queries are perfectly fine.
So that's cool isn't it.
So in this step what we look at Didn't named query and didn't name the Kuwaitis and the station name
is used when you want to just define one query.
But when you want to define multiple queries then you need to use a combination of named query and named
queries until the next step.
Boy.