Welcome back in one of the previous steps we looked at J.P. Cuil we looked at how to write Kuwaiti's
using J.P. Cuil.
And we can add them to name queries in the last.
Let's shift our attention to something called native Kuwaiti's.
Some of the times you have to use native queries to find queries to the database builder those situations
and also how you can fire and Integrity's so I copied the typical test and I'll call this native test.
Native Crace.
So native great is nothing but sending a direct Cuil out from you AJP.
So instead of typical where we talk about entities when we're talking about JP Kuehl we are writing
queries using entities so the kind of queries that we would be using typically would be looking like
selects the from courtsey.
However this same query exude as a need to query it would look something like select start from course.
Right so what we want to do now is we will want to be able to execute a query of this kind.
So let's start from code.
How do we do that.
For that we will need to use the nitty gritty is what all the other stuff you just present in here.
So all this is not really needed.
So JP Cuil basic Actually now it's no longer need.
Pretty basic.
Basically what we're doing in here.
So here the manager has create native query method.
So I can create a native query passing in the query that I would want to execute to the query which
I want to use is that ex-staff from Cox 2.
So here I would change this as well to select stuff from and Right-Click.
I don't want to use unit test you can see that Janet has succeeded.
And also you can see that to start from course it's being fired here.
So that's cool.
And let's see what the results are being printed in here.
Well here you can see that all the quotes are being properly however one of the things that you can
see is here that blank that object is being printed because it does not know which entity to map.
It is said you can tell the entity to map to by using the entity as the second parameter so I can say
code got glass and I'm saying that the results would be of the type called door glass.
So now if you x you'd be created you'd see that the TAKES IT Fein as well as I look at the logs.
This is about is the output that is being printed.
That's good.
So this is a very basic need to quit.
Right.
So there are at once needed queries that you can fire as well so you can create native query and I can
define bad divs as well so I can see where ID is equal to.
Question Mark and I can take QED that said paramita and I can see the position.
So the position here starts with one so I can say position one de-value I would want to set a thousand
one and I can get the results set and printed this.
So I need to create is that bad.
So I'm trying to get a specific code in here.
Or the output.
So this is the IDs question.
I'm getting a specific code.
You can see that there is only one code that is being printed that's taking 50 steps.
That's the one which has the ID of 10000 1.
That's the cause that's being printed in here.
Now I can also used named Bammy.
So it's sort of being something of this going but I content named parameters.
What is the name paramita.
So interesting question mark.
So using position I can use named benami So I'm seeing colon ID and giving it a name.
And here I can say said parameter ID as 10000.
So instead of using additional parameters 1 I'm using named paramita so Id ideas ten thousand one.
Now you see there's not really any change in the result because it's the exact clearly which we are
fighting in.
Except with a different approach.
So here ideas equal to call.
And in this step what we're doing is actually looking at a few things related to native queries.
These are actually all the scenarios where we are looking at right now are actually those things where
it's better to use the J-P Cuil.
But are there situations where you have to go for native queries.
Yes there are definitely situations where you have to go to do queries Sometimes you have to set some
tuning parameters or you want to use some database specific feature.
So if you're going to do a database and it has a feature which is not supported by Dhupia in those kind
of situations you have no other option other than trying to find any queries.
And the other situation where you'd have to go for a need to query is when you have to do a mass update.
Let's say I would want to abate all the rules ina specific table in a query.
In those kind of situations if you do it through AJP then you would need to get the dough.
And then about it get zero then I bet you cannot do a Masab day using JP.
So in those kind of situations we would use Nathu queries so the way we would do that let's say I would
want to update the ablated time stamp on all this stuff do queries to date.
So I would want to update all the rules in the course table so I would want to say update called said
I would want to say the updated date last updated date of all the columns.
Let's say I would want to set it persisted menu using an update then the baby would do that is by using
a query.
Execute it.
And this would be done in your back.
This would be done in a number of rows updated rules.
And now I can log in a number of rules update I can log the number of close update to see what would
happen.
So doing this kind of stuff.
JP is not really efficient because if you want to update this kind of stuff through JPA you need to
get the each row and then update go viral.
There's no way to do Masab that through.
You can see that I'm getting a transaction required here because we are trying to change the data.
You need a transaction.
And for this does that make it transactional transaction.
Ideally an underlying all of this which we're making changes to the database we were calling a repository
method and the transactional is defined on the repository method.
So there was no problem just the first time at our Click calling update from the chain itself.
So we needed that transaction to make sure that this is within the boundaries of a transaction.
And you can see that I'm seeing update got last updated that is equal to this date and you can see that
all of the four rows which are present in the database are updated to this step.
What we looked at is different kinds of native queries.
We can look at how to set parameters to native queries.
Also we looked at how big you can be using a need to create more of the things you'd need to make sure
that when I were using a query you're not making use of persistence context.
So if you have all these entities data present in your persistence context then you need to make sure
that you would refresh them so that you get the latest stuff from the database and then the next step.